Teguh Prabowo Wijangkoro

Programmer

Semarang, Jawa Tengah ID

□ teguh.pw20@gmail.com □ +6281215541064

negadive in Teguh Prabowo Wijangkoro



Experienced Back End Developer with a demonstrated history of working in the information technology and services industry. Skilled in SQL, PHP, C++, Object-Oriented Programming (OOP), and English. Strong engineering professional with a Bachelor's degree focused in Information System from Universitas Dian Nuswantoro.

SKILLS

Python Database Javascript

FastAPI MySql sqlite Pandas

WORK EXPERIENCE (3) -

Backend Developer at PT Talenta Informasi Teknologi

Mar 2020 - Current



Design and implement server-side features and API using FastAPI framework

- Involve in database structure decision making
- Integrate third party service like Firebase, Midtrans

Assistant Lecturer at Dian Nuswantoro University

Jan 2018 - Jan 2019



Assisting lecturer in Database course

Assistant Lecturer at Dian Nuswantoro University

Jan 2017 - Jan 2018



Assisting lecturer in Programming and Algorithm course

PROJECTS (5)

Golek Truk

Jan 2020 - Current

RESTful API MySQL Python FastAPI AWS S3 Docker

Build backend service. An advertisement service for Shippers and Truckers related without in-application transaction between seller and buyer.

- Collaborate with 1 other Backend Developer, 2 Frontend Developers, 2 Business Analysts
- Design and build REST API using FastAPI framework
- Design database, using MySQL
- Research and integrate Firebase Authentication for authentication service
- Research and integrate Midtrans for payment gateway
- MongoDB for logging service



- AWS S3 for uploaded file storage service
- Docker for deployment
- Git as Continous Integration

Siba Promoter

Apr 2020 - Nov 2020



Built two backend services; **(1)Interactive Web Trucker**, an application for promoting Siba's orders to the partners via Web Application or Telegram Chat Application. **(2)Backoffice**, a financial application that records the transaction **Interactive Web Trucker** invoices and bills and generate journals and reports

- Collaborate with 1 other Backend Developer, 1 Frontend Developer, 2 Business Analysts
- Integrate with CarLo via database level
- Design and build REST API using FastAPI framework
- Design database, using MySQL
- AWS S3 for uploaded file storage
- Docker for deployment
- Research and integrate with Telegram Bot API using python
- Git as Continous Integration

Pemesanan Online Tiket Wisata

Jun 2020 - Aug 2020

PHP MySQL HTML CSS JavaScript

Prototype aplikasi pemesanan tiket wisata secara online

Integrasi Sederhana Telegram-bot dan Google Spreadsheet

Feb 2020 - Feb 2020

JavaScript

Integrasi sederhana mengirim pesan setiap pembuatan row baru pada Google Spreadsheet

Aplikasi Recency, Frequency, Monetary (RFM)

Mar 2019 - Mar 2019

PHP HTML CSS JavaScript

Prototype aplikasi analisa RFM otomatis

EDUCATION (2)

Bachelor Information System at Dian Nuswantoro University

2016 - Current

Highschool Mekatronika at SMK Negeri 1 Batam

2012 - 2015

LANGUAGES

English

Intermediate

Indonesia

Native speaker